http://www.residex.com/privacy-policy

The health and safety of our customers is of paramount importance to us. Learn more about our response to COVID-19.
Effective Date: April 1, 2010
Target Specialty Products values and recognizes that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we may collect when you use the Web Site and Target Specialty Products Services. Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Target Specialty Products Web Site you are accepting the practices described in this policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@Target Specialty Products.com
Does Target Specialty Products Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?
We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by sending you an email (if you are aShopkeeper), posting a notice on the home page of the Web Site, or, through the use of cookies, informing you when you first sign on to the Web Site after we have made changes. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You will not be able to receive notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept.
What Types of Information Does Target Specialty Products Collect From Me? Personal Information.
We collect Personal Information from you. As explained above, Personal Information is information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and credit card number.
Non-Personal Information.
We also collect "non-personal" information from you,such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, and your IPAddress. This information ("Non-Personal Information") cannot be easily used to personally identify you.
How and When Does Target Specialty Products Collect This Information?
We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product sold through a Shop, we may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, credit card number, and email address. If you create an Account, we may collect your name, mailing address, email address, and other information that we request in the registration process. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address.
Analytic and Reporting Technologies.
Like the operators of most web sites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, click-stream patterns, and the dates and times that the Web Site and the Target Specialty Products Services are accessed.
How Does Target Specialty Products Use My Information?
We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Target Specialty Products Services and the Web Site, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, and providing customer support. For example, if you create an Account, we will use the information that you provide to communicate with you.
Non-Personal Information. We use non-personal information to track your use of the Web Site and the Target Specialty Products Services and for other internal purposes, particularly providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the Target Specialty Products Services and the Web Site.
When Will Target Specialty Products Disclose My Information to Third Parties?
Generally speaking, we do not intentionally disclose your information to third parties without your consent. However we reserve the right to do so because it is necessary to the operation and continued growth of our business or to protect the rights of others. These instances are discussed below:
Disclosure to Successors. We may disclose your Personal Information to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires us. In the event Target Specialty Products goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or by a notice on our Web Site of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.
Disclosure of Non-Personal Information. We will disclose Non-Personal Information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others.You may not "opt out" of the sharing of this information. However, it cannot be easily used to identify you personally.
What about cookies?
A cookie is a message that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Most web sites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Web Site and the Target Specialty Products Services, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to sign in and begin use of the Target Specialty Products Services automatically when you visit the Web Site. We may also use cookies to ensure that you have been notified of and agreed to the then-current version of the Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, and any other agreements and policies relating to your use of the Web Site or the Target Specialty Products Services. Cookies used by Target Specialty Products are not linked to Personal Information.
Does Target Specialty Products Protect My Personal Information?
Personal Information. Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.
Subscribe to The Target Advantage eNewsletter
Don't miss any important information to help you move forward!
Shop Online 24/7 from anywhere
Place orders and manage your account at your convenience.
Copyright © 2020, Target Specialty Products. All Rights Reserved. By using this website you agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.
